ANDRE BOULAY: So, the next trick we're going to show you is called leg orbits.
The yoyo is actually going up and around your leg.
It's pretty cool looking.
I'm going to show you what it looks like first.
Just throw the yoyo, just like so, you step over the string like that and we actually do is swing the yoyo around and we'll catch on the string just like that.
That's the leg orbit.
So, to do this trick, what you want to do is when you throw and you step over it.
This is where I'm going to stop the yoyo and show you what's happening real quick.
So, the yoyo is coming up over the string, it's being released off this hand.
This hand is pretty much propelling it.
So, when the yoyo is sitting here, I'm pulling with this hand which propels it off the string.
It comes over here and this hand helps guide it.
This hand's really not doing too much.
It's just sitting here, guiding it as the yoyo comes over.
If it's coming over this way, you're going to want to pull the string so it sits into it.
The minute the yoyo hits the string, it's just going to spin right down to the other side again, and this is where this hand comes and propels it back up over your leg where you once again guide it back down.
So practice that, get a good strong throw, and eventually, you'll be able to do this for a really long time, that's called leg orbit.